<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.7.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-11-02T15:52:17-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Rick’s Blog</title><subtitle>What's inside my head, in a digital sense.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Break The Stigma</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2018/06/break-the-stigma/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Break The Stigma" /><published>2018-06-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-06-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2018/06/break-the-stigma</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2018/06/break-the-stigma/">&lt;p&gt;Last Saturday, I ran in &lt;a href=&quot;https://my.hftd.org/chicago/events/the-humboldt-mile/e122051&quot;&gt;The Humboldt Mile&lt;/a&gt;.  A one mile (timed!) race to raise funds of and awareness of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hftd.org/&quot;&gt;Hope For The Day’s&lt;/a&gt; Proactive Suicide Prevention programs. It seems pretty insignificant that my $25 entry free and my 10ish minutes of running would do much to help suicide prevention, right?  Since I ran my eight-minute, sixteen-second mile, we’ve lost a groundbreaking fashion icon and a world-renowned chef, author, &amp;amp; storyteller by suicide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are the names you hear. These are the products you own. The shows you watch. Now everything has the all-too-early &lt;em&gt;posthumous&lt;/em&gt; tag, or &lt;em&gt;“since their death”&lt;/em&gt;, associated with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, there are thousands more every day that die to suicide. The world will never know them by name or face. But they do matter to their friends, their family, their loved ones. The thousands of souls will never fill our heart with their laughter again, never walk through our hallways, or meet us for dinner. All due to the time on this Earth being cut short, way too short.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is why we have to have these conversations to break the stigma of mental health, mental illness, and the healthcare access necessary for the support and treatment of both. It’s good to have the conversation when a name we recognize is in the news. But it’s even better to have the conversation on a random Thursday without any Hollywood headlines or famous people attached, completely removed from the 24-hour news cycle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Have the hard conversations.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Reach out to your struggling friend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Reach out to your strong friend.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Break the stigma.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For access to resources, please visit any of the following sites:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twloha.com/find-help/local-resources/&quot;&gt;To Write Love On Her Arms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hftd.org/find-help/&quot;&gt;Hope For The Day&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.crisistextline.org/&quot;&gt;Crisis Text Line&lt;/a&gt; - Text HOME to 741741 in the US&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://suicidepreventionlifeline.org/&quot;&gt;National Suicide Prevention Lifeline&lt;/a&gt; - 1-800-273-8255
​&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</content><author><name>Rick Osowski</name></author><category term="Mental Health" /><category term="Mental Illness" /><category term="Suicide Awareness" /><category term="Suicide Prevention" /><summary type="html">Last Saturday, I ran in The Humboldt Mile. A one mile (timed!) race to raise funds of and awareness of Hope For The Day’s Proactive Suicide Prevention programs. It seems pretty insignificant that my $25 entry free and my 10ish minutes of running would do much to help suicide prevention, right? Since I ran my eight-minute, sixteen-second mile, we’ve lost a groundbreaking fashion icon and a world-renowned chef, author, &amp;amp; storyteller by suicide.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">#ThankYourMentor</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/02/thank-your-mentor/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="#ThankYourMentor" /><published>2016-02-08T03:15:33-06:00</published><updated>2016-02-08T03:15:33-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2016/02/thank-your-mentor</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2016/02/thank-your-mentor/">&lt;p&gt;To say I traveled a lot in 2015 would be an understatement.  But some of that came with the benefit of fruitfully killing time in the airport.  One day when walking through DFW and checking Twitter, I happened across my dear friend Moe’s Twitter/LinkedIn &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/moeabdula/status/630044688284647424&quot;&gt;share&lt;/a&gt; of a &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#ThankYourMentor&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt; post detailing to “&lt;em&gt;Focus on Your Character, Not Your Career&lt;/em&gt;”, inspired by the original author’s parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was pretty serendipitous that Moe shared this post, as he’s been my most influential &amp;amp; prolific mentor to date, so I figured I’d follow up with 3 things here that I learned from him and working with him; things that have helped me be successful every day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;1-starting-out-just-say-yes&quot;&gt;1.  Starting out, just say Yes!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is something so simple, but everyone isn’t always in tune with what this actually means.  I’m a very &lt;em&gt;“learn by doing”&lt;/em&gt; person, so if I can jump at the chance to work through a project, I will.  But if it’s not my area or something I’m responsible for, either in a new area or just starting, I’ll stay with it to find the right person, the right answer, the right solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may not always be the best for my multi-tasking focus, but it has always helped me to learn at an incredible pace, bring teammates up with me, and become a respected advisor for many peers across the IT landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;2-learn-to-say-no-but-for-practical-reasons&quot;&gt;2.  Learn to say no, but for practical reasons&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contrasting #1 above, you will eventually need to learn to say no.  But not because you don’t want to do it, you don’t know how, or you don’t understand something, but because it’s more beneficial for a team member to accomplish the task for some reason or another.  Often in large companies, once you are known for being good at something, you get stuck as the “&lt;em&gt;go to&lt;/em&gt;” person for that role.  But you may, in fact, have moved on from the role a long time ago.  Instead of saying yes, work with all parties involved to make sure the colleagues with needs are connected to the folks that can solve those problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This isn’t always apparently clear when you make the switch, and it’s definitely a grey area when you can start, but you’ll eventually know when it feels right and when to be maximizing your potential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;3-dont-shy-away-from-things-youre-not-good-at-they-will-be-your-strength-in-the-future&quot;&gt;3.  Don’t shy away from things you’re not good at. They will be your strength in the future.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This, to me, is the most important thing I’ve learned from Moe.  Many times over I have been presented with a project that I just had to figure out - ranging from demos to presentations to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J99jjeH8XZs&quot;&gt;keynotes&lt;/a&gt;.  These are things that just have to get figured out, often because someone who sees much more of what you are capable of than yourself, wants to push you in the right direction.  Not every swing is going to be a home run, not every project is going to be a success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As I said, I learn by doing very well, and running head long into these projects, while often scary, has been the most rewarding part of my career and I can’t thank Moe enough for believing in me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;going-forward&quot;&gt;Going forward&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All of these things I learned first hand from working with Moe and have often relayed them to new colleagues, in both words &amp;amp; action.  It’s a strange feeling when you recognize strengths or successes that you hadn’t really ever acknowledged or were aware of, but it is definitely a gratifying feeling and something that makes the hard cross-team work &amp;amp; brain teasers worth it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rick Osowski</name></author><category term="Career" /><category term="Learning" /><category term="Thank You" /><category term="ThankYourMentor" /><summary type="html">To say I traveled a lot in 2015 would be an understatement.  But some of that came with the benefit of fruitfully killing time in the airport.  One day when walking through DFW and checking Twitter, I happened across my dear friend Moe’s Twitter/LinkedIn share of a #ThankYourMentor  post detailing to “Focus on Your Character, Not Your Career”, inspired by the original author’s parents.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">2015 – A Productive Year</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2016/01/twenty-fifteen-a-productive-year/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="2015 &amp;#8211; A Productive Year" /><published>2016-01-11T05:15:12-06:00</published><updated>2016-01-11T05:15:12-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2016/01/twenty-fifteen-a-productive-year</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2016/01/twenty-fifteen-a-productive-year/">&lt;p&gt;This past year was an awfully productive year, with plenty of unexpected opportunities for publishing some content.  As I’m prone to going back and searching for my own content, I figured a year-end post (that is only a week late) would be a perfect opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Starting off the year, working with numerous colleagues, we published some labs for using Docker Containers and Cloud Foundry runtimes to manage Web App Hosting Workloads.  These are severely dated as of now, but I wanted to include them for history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;actionable-architecture-web-application-hosting-using-containers&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/bluemix/docs/actionable-architecture-building-web-application-hosting-containers/&quot;&gt;Actionable Architecture: Web application hosting using containers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;actionable-architecture-web-application-hosting-using-cloud-foundry&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/bluemix/docs/actionable-architecture-building-web-application-hosting-cloud-foundry/&quot;&gt;Actionable Architecture: Web application hosting using Cloud Foundry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, we followed up with some Big Data on Cloud work and published a lab for running some hybrid data scenarios on Bluemix&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;how-big-is-big-data-get-hands-on-experience-today&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/bluemix/2015/06/16/how-big-is-big-data/&quot;&gt;How big is Big Data? Get hands-on experience today&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;actionable-architecture-secure-hybrid-data-warehouse-on-bluemix&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/bluemix/docs/actionable-architecture-secure-hybrid-data-warehouse-bluemix-big-data-workshop-1/&quot;&gt;Actionable Architecture: Secure Hybrid Data Warehouse on Bluemix&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, I kicked off an article series on DeveloperWorks for microservices, titled &lt;strong&gt;“Microservices In Action”&lt;/strong&gt;.  This would be the first step in my microservices journey for the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;microservices-in-action-part-1-introduction-to-microservices&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ibm.com/developerworks/cloud/library/cl-bluemix-microservices-in-action-part-1-trs/index.html&quot;&gt;Microservices In Action, Part 1: Introduction to microservices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Supporting some of my peers attending DockerCon NA 2015 in San Francisco, I published a couple blog posts on Docker, containers, and what we were doing with reference architectures through the first half of 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;the-power-of-containers-in-bringing-reference-architectures-to-life&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/opentech/2015/06/19/the-power-of-containers-in-bringing-reference-architectures-to-life/&quot;&gt;The Power of Containers in Bringing Reference Architectures to Life!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following up on some of the problems solved in our labs and looking at reusable scenarios, I published a pretty popular article on how to feasibly use IBM Bluemix services inside a container, running on IBM Containers in Bluemix.  This one was pretty spot on at the time and still is very popular as of today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ibm-containers-and-bluemix-services--simplifying-distributed-docker-applications-at-runtime&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/bluemix/2015/07/06/simplifying-distributed-docker-applications/&quot;&gt;IBM Containers and Bluemix Services – simplifying distributed Docker applications at runtime&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Following up on my Microservices In Action series, I published a second post in time for DockerCon EU 2015 in November.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;microservices-in-action-part-2-containers-and-microservices--a-perfect-pair&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ibm.com/developerworks/cloud/library/cl-bluemix-microservices-in-action-part-2-trs/index.html&quot;&gt;Microservices In Action, Part 2: Containers and microservices — a perfect pair&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, just in time for DockerCon EU 2015, we launched &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/tv/microservices/&quot;&gt;microservicesTV&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, a video series to cover all things business and technical about microservices in the enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;microservicestv---all-things-microservices&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.ibm.com/tv/microservices/&quot;&gt;microservicesTV - All Things Microservices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/custom-media/CUleAm6XIAE8-Z3.png-large-300x150.png&quot; alt=&quot;microservicesTV - All things microservices&quot; width=&quot;300&quot; height=&quot;150&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I planned to write a lot more here (rickosowski.com) over the course of the year, but got sidetracked with all of the above.  I’m sure I missed a few things that happened in 2015, but am committing to publishing more than 3 posts here for 2016…&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rick Osowski</name></author><category term="Bluemix" /><category term="Cloud" /><category term="Docker" /><category term="Microservices" /><category term="YearInReview" /><summary type="html">This past year was an awfully productive year, with plenty of unexpected opportunities for publishing some content.  As I’m prone to going back and searching for my own content, I figured a year-end post (that is only a week late) would be a perfect opportunity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Go to a Meetup - like yesterday!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/06/go-to-a-meetup-like-yesterday/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Go to a Meetup - like yesterday!" /><published>2015-06-29T17:19:16-05:00</published><updated>2015-06-29T17:19:16-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/06/go-to-a-meetup-like-yesterday</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/06/go-to-a-meetup-like-yesterday/">&lt;p&gt;The concept of a Meetup isn’t anything new.  It’s been around tech circles for a while in the form of a User Group.  But the term &lt;em&gt;User Group&lt;/em&gt; suggested some amount of time invested into the technology or a certain level of expertise.  If I am completely new, what business do I have going to a &lt;em&gt;User Group&lt;/em&gt; where people are actually users!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a couple things I’ve learned since I’ve started attending Meetups across the country, as I travel for work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;go-to-meetups-to-learn&quot;&gt;Go to Meetups to learn&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meetups have become much like the campfires of the Wild West.  Everyone comes to tell their stories and listen to everyone else’s stories.  You don’t need to be an expert to attend a Meetup.  Just have an interest and be willing to learn.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You like beer?  There’s a meetup for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You like food?  There’s a meetup for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You like to code?  There’s a meetup for that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;em&gt;Hint:&lt;/em&gt;  There’s generally going to be meetups that let you do all three at once)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There isn’t going to be a better experience for “learn by doing” than a Meetup for most technology today.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;attendance-does-not-mean-participation&quot;&gt;Attendance does not mean participation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the Meetups I have attended over the past 18 months have had a pretty good distribution of “newbies” to “experienced users”.  It doesn’t hurt to start your meetup with some level setting information:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sign up URLs&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Getting started links&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;One-pager of terms&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Recap of last meetup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As humans, we’re more likely to admit we didn’t know something after you tell us rather than speaking up before hand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Just because someone is attending your Meetup, that does not mean they have registered for your service or product, let alone used it in any way&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;the-death-of-release-notes&quot;&gt;The Death of Release Notes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As software is becoming more continuously delivered and more continuously released, it makes it more difficult to disseminate change information.  In the 5 years my product heavily depended on WebSphere Application Server, I can count the number of Release Notes documents I read on one finger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;As product updates are released, they should be accompanied with blogs and videos from the product teams.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you run Meetups, plan your weekly or regularly scheduled topics around your product releases to cover the updates.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nothing is worse than exposing new users to mass confusion when experienced users don’t agree with breaking changes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;going-forward&quot;&gt;Going forward&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meetups are a great change to engaging a community previously left to Message Boards and Bug Trackers.  As new technologies pop up and persist, their associated Meetups will grow across the world as well.  It’s the rebirth of face to face communication, alongside not instead of technology.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to let me know of Meetups you’ve attended or plan to or would like to see.  I’ll be posting in the &lt;em&gt;Meetups&lt;/em&gt; category as I attend more throughout the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rick Osowski</name></author><category term="Community" /><category term="Learning" /><category term="Meetups" /><summary type="html">The concept of a Meetup isn’t anything new.  It’s been around tech circles for a while in the form of a User Group.  But the term User Group suggested some amount of time invested into the technology or a certain level of expertise.  If I am completely new, what business do I have going to a User Group where people are actually users!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">On Podcasts</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/06/on-podcasts/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On Podcasts" /><published>2015-05-31T19:21:25-05:00</published><updated>2015-05-31T19:21:25-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/06/on-podcasts</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/06/on-podcasts/">&lt;p&gt;This post is tangentially related to technology, so I figured I would share it, even if it’s not going to be the main focus of my writing here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve been a big fan of podcasts since they became more consumable about 7 years back, right around the same time the first iPhone was released.  In any given week, I am either binge listening to music albums I forgot I had or catching up on multiple episodes of a handful of podcasts.  Being a music lover for as long as I can remember, my appreciation for the long form interview has grown very much in time with the popularity of podcasts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are many different types of podcasts out there, but my favorite genre tends to be comedy, usually with one or two hosts and different guests.  Anywhere from 30 minutes to a couple hours, each podcast episode can provide as much entertainment as a summer blockbuster, with a new one coming in just a couple days.  The two main podcasts I keep track of are &lt;a href=&quot;http://smodcast.com/channels/tell-em-steve-dave/&quot;&gt;Tell ‘Em Steve Dave&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://nerdist.com/tag/you-made-it-weird/&quot;&gt;You Made It Weird with Pete Holmes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to the frequency TESD publishes, I listen to their new weekly episode each and every week as soon as it is available.  With YMIW, I tend to let them queue up and listen to them in bunches (especially when traveling for work), as they are normally released a few times a week.  The most pleasant surprise has been conversations and guests that I would normally not care for and skip the episode, but giving it a shot anyway &amp;amp; coming away with an amazing and new appreciation for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Case in point, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-263-noel-gallagher/&quot;&gt;recent episode of YMIW with Noel Gallagher&lt;/a&gt;.  I wasn’t sure how much I would be intrigued to keep listening, but I was going to be in the car, so I let it roll.  To say I felt ashamed for doubting Pete and/or Noel, would be a bit of an understatement.  This episode was mind-blowing on many levels, and this is on the back of some YMIW episodes in the past 6 months that will forever remain in my Podcasts app to come back to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-253-richard-rohr/&quot;&gt;Richard Rohr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-243-henry-rollins/&quot;&gt;Henry Rollins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-238-peter-rollins/&quot;&gt;Peter Rollins&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And these are just a few of the recent episodes that I can call out specifically.  Each and everyone has me laughing in stitches and thinking with a new perspective on many topics I previously didn’t really want to examine my own stance on.  Some of the older episodes also helped me to navigate my own thoughts and feelings when I needed something to bounce them off of.  Whatever was going on inside my head and I couldn’t identify it, listening to YMIW (often in backlog as I was coming in about 2 years late), I would find an episode and Pete &amp;amp; guest would knock it out of the park, nailing exactly what I was feeling on the head.  Some of these episodes were:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-131-matt-mira/&quot;&gt;Matt Mira&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-22-emily-gordon/&quot;&gt;Emily Gordon&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-172-whitney-cummings/&quot;&gt;Whitney Cummings&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://nerdist.com/you-made-it-weird-2-tj-miller/&quot;&gt;TJ Miller&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you take nothing else away from this post, I would want it to be to not judge a book by it’s cover, or in this instance, a podcast episode on the guest.  Similar to when I can actually keep up with &lt;a href=&quot;https://nerdist.com/podcasts/nerdist-podcast-channel/&quot;&gt;The Nerdist Podcast&lt;/a&gt;, as Chris Hardwick says, there’s a good reason the guest is on the show, so give them a shot and see what they have to say.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just want to say &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;thank you!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; to Pete and everyone at YMIW for the hours and hours of truly amazing content.  Keep up the great work.  I look forward to many more hours of free funny, as well as eye-opening and thought-provoking episodes that I can listen to, with tears of laughter rolling down my face, while anyone traveling with me thinks I am losing my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even with the random chance of not hitting next on the phone when I was in the car today, I’m left with a quote from Noel Gallagher that I can’t get out of my head and have the burning desire to get on a wall hanging of some sort:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;lifes-too-short-to-worry-about-the-answer&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Life’s too short to worry about the answer”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;</content><author><name>Rick Osowski</name></author><category term="Podcasts" /><category term="Tangent" /><category term="TESD" /><category term="YMIW" /><summary type="html">This post is tangentially related to technology, so I figured I would share it, even if it’s not going to be the main focus of my writing here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Starting over…</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2015/05/starting-over-2/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Starting over..." /><published>2015-05-22T07:28:06-05:00</published><updated>2015-05-22T07:28:06-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2015/05/starting-over</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2015/05/starting-over-2/">&lt;p&gt;This is my first post… for about the ninth time.  Hopefully, this time it sticks since I’ve run out of blogging lives.  I’ll be more committed to posting on technology, travel, and other items I find interesting (which you probably will not).&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Rick Osowski</name></author><summary type="html">This is my first post… for about the ninth time.  Hopefully, this time it sticks since I’ve run out of blogging lives.  I’ll be more committed to posting on technology, travel, and other items I find interesting (which you probably will not).</summary></entry></feed>